Mike Wallace Papers
Mike Wallace Papers
- The Hate That Hate Produced (documentary)
  - VHS (Copy 2), wallace_m_290; Videotape, VHS (Box 13)
Shirer, Williamscript, Nov 29 1960 recording, undated
Shirley MacLaine recording, undated
Shor, Tootsscript, May 15 1959 recording, undated
Shulman, Charles (Dr. and Rabbi) recording, undated
Sillman, Leonardscript, Oct 23 1959 recording, undated
Sinatra, Frank recording, undated
Skinner, Cornelia Otisscript, Oct 2 1959 recording, undated
Smith, Harry Allenscript, Mar 14 1960 recording, undated
Smith, A. Merrimanrecording, undated script, Feb 10 1961
Sokolsky, Georgescript, Mar 9 1960 recording, 3/21/1960 recording, 3/22/1960
Soraci, Carmeloscript, Apr 6 1961 recording, undated
Soustelle, Jacquesscript, Mar 30 1960 recording, undated
St. John, Robertscript, Oct 18 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Stapleton, Maureenscript, May 1 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Steiger, Rodscript, Nov 22 1960 recording, undated
Sterling, Janscript, Mar 16 1960 recording, 3/30/1960
Stern, Billscript, Oct 9 1959 recording, undated
Stern, Isaacscript, Jan 12 1961 recording, 1/11/1961
Stevens, Ingerscript, Dec 20 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Stevens, Lesliescript, Apr 6 1960 (?) recording, undated
Stevenson, Adlai script, Sep 14 1959
Stone, Willisscript, Oct 11 1960 recording, undated
Stritch, Elaine script, Mar 12 1959 (?)
Styne, Julescript, Mar 2 1960 recording, 3/14/1960
Susskind, Davidscripts, Apr 28 1959, Sep 20 1960 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated
Sziliard, Leo recording, undated
Taylor, Elizabeth recording, undated
Taylor, Reneescript, Jan 6 1961 recording, undated
Tillstrom, Burrscript, Nov 8 1960 recording, undated
Todd, Mike Jr.recording, undated script, Feb 11 1960
de Toledano, Ralphscript, Apr 29 1960 recording, undated
Torme, Melscript, Feb 17 1961 recording, 2/17/1961
Tracy, Vincentscript, Jan 5 1961 recording, 1/5/1961
Trapp, Maria scripts, Dec 6 1960, Dec 20 1960
Umeki, Myoshiscript, Apr 20 1959 recording, undated
Uphous, Willardscript, dec 13 1960 recording, undated
Ustinov, Peterscript, Jul 21 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Vallee, Rudyscript, Jul 14 1959 recording, undated
Van Dyke, Dickscript, Feb 17 1961 recording, 2/17/1961
van Fleet, James (General)script, Jun 9 1959 recording, undated
Van Horne, Harrietscript, Apr 29 1960 recording, undated
Van Rensselaer, Philipscript, Apr 15 1960 recording, undated
Vanderbilt, Amyscript, Nov 25 1959 recording, undated recording, undated
Veeck, Billscript, Jan 24 1960 recording, undated
Vidal, Gorescripts, May 8 1959, Apr 18 1960, Dec 12 1960, Dec 13 1960 recording, undated recording, undated
Vidic, Dobrivije recording, undated
Vidie, Ambassador D. script, Mar 17 1960
Wagner, Robert F.recording, undated script, Jan 25 1960
Walcott, Joe ("Jersey Joe")script, Aug 1959 (?) recording, undated
Walker, Nancyscript, Feb 3 1961 recording, undated
Wallach, Eliscripts, Dec 4 1959, Jan 26 1961 recording, undated
Waters, Ethelscript, Apr 9 1959 recording, undated
Waugh, Alecscript, Apr 8 1960 recording, undated
Weaver, Sylvester recording, undated
Wechsler, Jamesscript, May 23 1960 recording, undated
Wertham, Fredricrecording, Feb-60 scripts, Jan 28 1960, Apr 25 1960, Nov 1 1960 recording, 3/15/1960 recording, undated recording, undated recording, undated
Wheeler, Bertscript, May 5 1959 recording, undated
Whiteman, Paulscript, May 18 1960 recording, undated
Williams, G. Mennenrecording, undated script, Apr 15 1959
Williams, Tennessee script, Nov 14 1960
Winters, Jonathanscript, Mar 25 1960 recording, undated
Wismer, Harryscript, Nov 8 1960 recording, undated
Wiznitzer, Louis script, Oct 18 1960
Workman, William recording, 3/1/1960
Wright, Frank Lloydrecording, undated recording, undated
Wright, Olgivanna recording, undated
Wyman, Louisscript, Dec 19 1960 recording, undated
Youngman, Hennyscript, Jan 26 1961 recording, undated
Zolotow, Mauricescripts, Apr 4 1960, Nov 14 1960 recording, undated recording, undated